{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::numbers_counting_song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685952641","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685952640"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203759"," gameId":" b97aa7a3-2fa8-4f25-b2c5-b963a18b4b61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Moja mbili tatu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::numbers_counting_song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685953150","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685953150"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203759"," gameId":" b97aa7a3-2fa8-4f25-b2c5-b963a18b4b61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Moja mbili tatu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBILI"," userResponse":" MBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::numbers_counting_song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685953951","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685953951"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203759"," gameId":" b97aa7a3-2fa8-4f25-b2c5-b963a18b4b61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Moja mbili tatu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::numbers_counting_song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685956836","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685956836"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203759"," gameId":" b97aa7a3-2fa8-4f25-b2c5-b963a18b4b61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nne tano sita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NNE"," userResponse":" NNE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::numbers_counting_song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685957406","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685957406"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203759"," gameId":" b97aa7a3-2fa8-4f25-b2c5-b963a18b4b61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nne tano sita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::numbers_counting_song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685958163","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685958163"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203759"," gameId":" b97aa7a3-2fa8-4f25-b2c5-b963a18b4b61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nne tano sita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SITA"," userResponse":" SITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::numbers_counting_song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685961107","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685961107"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203759"," gameId":" b97aa7a3-2fa8-4f25-b2c5-b963a18b4b61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Saba nane tisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABA"," userResponse":" SABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::numbers_counting_song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685961684","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685961682"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203759"," gameId":" b97aa7a3-2fa8-4f25-b2c5-b963a18b4b61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Saba nane tisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANE"," userResponse":" NANE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::numbers_counting_song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685962479","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685962479"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203759"," gameId":" b97aa7a3-2fa8-4f25-b2c5-b963a18b4b61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Saba nane tisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TISA"," userResponse":" TISA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::numbers_counting_song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685965622","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685965622"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203759"," gameId":" b97aa7a3-2fa8-4f25-b2c5-b963a18b4b61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sifuri ni bila."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIFURI"," userResponse":" SIFURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::numbers_counting_song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685965881","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685965881"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203759"," gameId":" b97aa7a3-2fa8-4f25-b2c5-b963a18b4b61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sifuri ni bila."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::numbers_counting_song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685966591","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685966591"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203759"," gameId":" b97aa7a3-2fa8-4f25-b2c5-b963a18b4b61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sifuri ni bila."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" BILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::numbers_counting_song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685969458","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685969457"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203759"," gameId":" b97aa7a3-2fa8-4f25-b2c5-b963a18b4b61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Moja mbili tatu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::numbers_counting_song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685969964","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685969964"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203759"," gameId":" b97aa7a3-2fa8-4f25-b2c5-b963a18b4b61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Moja mbili tatu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBILI"," userResponse":" MBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::numbers_counting_song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685970760","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685970760"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203759"," gameId":" b97aa7a3-2fa8-4f25-b2c5-b963a18b4b61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Moja mbili tatu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::numbers_counting_song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685973667","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685973666"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203759"," gameId":" b97aa7a3-2fa8-4f25-b2c5-b963a18b4b61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nne tano sita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NNE"," userResponse":" NNE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::numbers_counting_song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685974260","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685974259"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203759"," gameId":" b97aa7a3-2fa8-4f25-b2c5-b963a18b4b61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nne tano sita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::numbers_counting_song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685975036","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685975035"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203759"," gameId":" b97aa7a3-2fa8-4f25-b2c5-b963a18b4b61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nne tano sita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SITA"," userResponse":" SITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::numbers_counting_song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685978000","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685977999"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203759"," gameId":" b97aa7a3-2fa8-4f25-b2c5-b963a18b4b61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Saba nane tisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABA"," userResponse":" SABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::numbers_counting_song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685978579","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685978579"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203759"," gameId":" b97aa7a3-2fa8-4f25-b2c5-b963a18b4b61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Saba nane tisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANE"," userResponse":" NANE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::numbers_counting_song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685979367","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685979367"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203759"," gameId":" b97aa7a3-2fa8-4f25-b2c5-b963a18b4b61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Saba nane tisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TISA"," userResponse":" TISA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::numbers_counting_song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685982145","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685982144"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203759"," gameId":" b97aa7a3-2fa8-4f25-b2c5-b963a18b4b61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kumi ni vidole!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMI"," userResponse":" KUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::numbers_counting_song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685982414","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685982414"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203759"," gameId":" b97aa7a3-2fa8-4f25-b2c5-b963a18b4b61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kumi ni vidole!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::numbers_counting_song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685983201","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685983200"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203759"," gameId":" b97aa7a3-2fa8-4f25-b2c5-b963a18b4b61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kumi ni vidole!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIDOLE"," userResponse":" VIDOLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::numbers_counting_song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685986449","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685986447"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203759"," gameId":" b97aa7a3-2fa8-4f25-b2c5-b963a18b4b61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Kumi ni vidole!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685986544","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685986544"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203759"," gameId":" b97aa7a3-2fa8-4f25-b2c5-b963a18b4b61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kumi ni vidole!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIDOLE"," userResponse":" VIDOLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543685998560","data":{"timestamp":" 1543685998560"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203759"," gameId":" 4ecdee3a-3c96-4d53-8ea6-eda01f40e422"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_M-D-Z"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543686000079","data":{"timestamp":" 1543686000078"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203759"," gameId":" 4ecdee3a-3c96-4d53-8ea6-eda01f40e422"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_M-D-Z"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543686027056","data":{"timestamp":" 1543686027056"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203759"," gameId":" e1c41a88-75f6-4e7f-8f6d-67f9d462547f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543686053229","data":{"timestamp":" 1543686053229"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203759"," gameId":" e1c41a88-75f6-4e7f-8f6d-67f9d462547f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543686053406","data":{"timestamp":" 1543686053406"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203759"," gameId":" e1c41a88-75f6-4e7f-8f6d-67f9d462547f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sio ya kijani kibichi kila wakati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543686064439","data":{"timestamp":" 1543686064438"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203759"," gameId":" e1c41a88-75f6-4e7f-8f6d-67f9d462547f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Sio ya kijani kibichi kila wakati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543686075008","data":{"timestamp":" 1543686075008"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203759"," gameId":" 2a95da7e-7ff8-4517-82ed-5cb7ee450675"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" START"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543686076311","data":{"timestamp":" 1543686076310"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203759"," gameId":" 2a95da7e-7ff8-4517-82ed-5cb7ee450675"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543686076401","data":{"timestamp":" 1543686076401"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203759"," gameId":" 2a95da7e-7ff8-4517-82ed-5cb7ee450675"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ENDPROBLEM"," userResponse":" ENDPROBLEM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" ENDPROBLEM"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543686089464","data":{"timestamp":" 1543686089464"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203759"," gameId":" 6e3e05f6-2466-4007-a257-f2e45312961d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_V-K-F"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543686092928","data":{"timestamp":" 1543686092928"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203759"," gameId":" 6e3e05f6-2466-4007-a257-f2e45312961d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_M_S-P-M"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543686096410","data":{"timestamp":" 1543686096410"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203759"," gameId":" 6e3e05f6-2466-4007-a257-f2e45312961d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_N_G-N-CH"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543686100002","data":{"timestamp":" 1543686100002"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203759"," gameId":" 6e3e05f6-2466-4007-a257-f2e45312961d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_J-A-R"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543686103460","data":{"timestamp":" 1543686103460"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203759"," gameId":" 6e3e05f6-2466-4007-a257-f2e45312961d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_I-W-O"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543686107245","data":{"timestamp":" 1543686107245"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203759"," gameId":" 6e3e05f6-2466-4007-a257-f2e45312961d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_B-A-L"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543686112259","data":{"timestamp":" 1543686112259"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203759"," gameId":" 6e3e05f6-2466-4007-a257-f2e45312961d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_P-F-L"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543686121547","data":{"timestamp":" 1543686121547"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203759"," gameId":" 6e3e05f6-2466-4007-a257-f2e45312961d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_P-F-L"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543686125176","data":{"timestamp":" 1543686125175"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203759"," gameId":" 6e3e05f6-2466-4007-a257-f2e45312961d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_K_J-K-Y"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543686130508","data":{"timestamp":" 1543686130507"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203759"," gameId":" 6e3e05f6-2466-4007-a257-f2e45312961d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_P-Z-A"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543686136652","data":{"timestamp":" 1543686136651"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203759"," gameId":" 6e3e05f6-2466-4007-a257-f2e45312961d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_P-Z-A"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543686141229","data":{"timestamp":" 1543686141229"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203759"," gameId":" 6e3e05f6-2466-4007-a257-f2e45312961d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_J-A-CH"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543686145101","data":{"timestamp":" 1543686145101"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203759"," gameId":" 6e3e05f6-2466-4007-a257-f2e45312961d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_O-G-S"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543686150101","data":{"timestamp":" 1543686150100"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203759"," gameId":" 6e3e05f6-2466-4007-a257-f2e45312961d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_R_B-R-T"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543686153691","data":{"timestamp":" 1543686153691"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203759"," gameId":" 6e3e05f6-2466-4007-a257-f2e45312961d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_M-I-CH"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543686157324","data":{"timestamp":" 1543686157324"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203759"," gameId":" 6e3e05f6-2466-4007-a257-f2e45312961d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_E_E-Y-R"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543686160749","data":{"timestamp":" 1543686160749"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203759"," gameId":" 6e3e05f6-2466-4007-a257-f2e45312961d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_H-B-Y"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543686164029","data":{"timestamp":" 1543686164029"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203759"," gameId":" 6e3e05f6-2466-4007-a257-f2e45312961d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_B-T-K"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543686168259","data":{"timestamp":" 1543686168259"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203759"," gameId":" 6e3e05f6-2466-4007-a257-f2e45312961d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_M-CH-L"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543686172166","data":{"timestamp":" 1543686172165"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203759"," gameId":" 6e3e05f6-2466-4007-a257-f2e45312961d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Y_G-N-Y"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543686175525","data":{"timestamp":" 1543686175525"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203759"," gameId":" 6e3e05f6-2466-4007-a257-f2e45312961d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_F-U-S"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543686179036","data":{"timestamp":" 1543686179036"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203759"," gameId":" 6e3e05f6-2466-4007-a257-f2e45312961d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_E-T-Y"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543686182642","data":{"timestamp":" 1543686182642"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203759"," gameId":" 6e3e05f6-2466-4007-a257-f2e45312961d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_N-D-I"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543686186410","data":{"timestamp":" 1543686186410"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203759"," gameId":" 6e3e05f6-2466-4007-a257-f2e45312961d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_G-O-T"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543686190732","data":{"timestamp":" 1543686190732"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203759"," gameId":" 6e3e05f6-2466-4007-a257-f2e45312961d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_M-D-Z"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543686194232","data":{"timestamp":" 1543686194231"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203759"," gameId":" 6e3e05f6-2466-4007-a257-f2e45312961d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_W_S-D-W"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543686200029","data":{"timestamp":" 1543686200028"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203759"," gameId":" 6e3e05f6-2466-4007-a257-f2e45312961d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_W_S-D-W"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543686278550","data":{"timestamp":" 1543686278550"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203759"," gameId":" e6622ccd-e172-4c00-a890-3580882bbf01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chungwa_hai-chungwa-nafuu-panda"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" chungwa"," userResponse":" chungwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543686295220","data":{"timestamp":" 1543686295220"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203759"," gameId":" e6622ccd-e172-4c00-a890-3580882bbf01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chungwa_nafuu-bata-naam-chungwa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" chungwa"," userResponse":" chungwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543686311771","data":{"timestamp":" 1543686311771"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203759"," gameId":" e6622ccd-e172-4c00-a890-3580882bbf01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" manjano_manjano-hizi-mungu-acha"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" manjano"," userResponse":" manjano"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543686329968","data":{"timestamp":" 1543686329968"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203759"," gameId":" e6622ccd-e172-4c00-a890-3580882bbf01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" manjano_a-samawati-manjano-u"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" manjano"," userResponse":" samawati"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543686336018","data":{"timestamp":" 1543686336018"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203759"," gameId":" e6622ccd-e172-4c00-a890-3580882bbf01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" manjano_a-samawati-manjano-u"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" manjano"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543686339895","data":{"timestamp":" 1543686339895"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203759"," gameId":" e6622ccd-e172-4c00-a890-3580882bbf01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" manjano_a-samawati-manjano-u"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" manjano"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543686343678","data":{"timestamp":" 1543686343678"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203759"," gameId":" e6622ccd-e172-4c00-a890-3580882bbf01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" manjano_a-samawati-manjano-u"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" manjano"," userResponse":" samawati"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543686347173","data":{"timestamp":" 1543686347172"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203759"," gameId":" e6622ccd-e172-4c00-a890-3580882bbf01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" manjano_a-samawati-manjano-u"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" manjano"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543686350505","data":{"timestamp":" 1543686350505"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203759"," gameId":" e6622ccd-e172-4c00-a890-3580882bbf01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" manjano_a-samawati-manjano-u"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" manjano"," userResponse":" manjano"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543686414512","data":{"timestamp":" 1543686414512"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203759"," gameId":" e6622ccd-e172-4c00-a890-3580882bbf01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kijani_kijani-tofauti-gani-uko"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" kijani"," userResponse":" kijani"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543686691058","data":{"timestamp":" 1543686691058"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203759"," gameId":" e6622ccd-e172-4c00-a890-3580882bbf01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" kijani_kijani-tofauti-gani-uko"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543686691207","data":{"timestamp":" 1543686691207"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203759"," gameId":" e6622ccd-e172-4c00-a890-3580882bbf01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miwa ni rangi ya ____________."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ____________"," userResponse":" KIJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543686699257","data":{"timestamp":" 1543686699257"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203759"," gameId":" e6622ccd-e172-4c00-a890-3580882bbf01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Miwa ni rangi ya ____________."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::1..4.SS_OFF1_INC.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543686705786","data":{"timestamp":" 1543686705785"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203759"," gameId":" e6622ccd-e172-4c00-a890-3580882bbf01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Miwa ni rangi ya ____________."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543686714146","data":{"timestamp":" 1543686714146"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203759"," gameId":" e6622ccd-e172-4c00-a890-3580882bbf01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Miwa ni rangi ya ____________."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543686754606","data":{"timestamp":" 1543686754606"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203759"," gameId":" 551ffdaa-8932-4e5e-808a-d673cb4afcc4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vile_maji-nguvu-kitu-vile"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" vile"," userResponse":" vile"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543686838998","data":{"timestamp":" 1543686838998"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203759"," gameId":" 551ffdaa-8932-4e5e-808a-d673cb4afcc4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" makali_dereva-hizi-huwa-makali"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" makali"," userResponse":" makali"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543686871280","data":{"timestamp":" 1543686871280"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203759"," gameId":" 551ffdaa-8932-4e5e-808a-d673cb4afcc4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" gani_nani-mwalimu-gani-ambayo"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" gani"," userResponse":" gani"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543686896435","data":{"timestamp":" 1543686896435"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203759"," gameId":" 551ffdaa-8932-4e5e-808a-d673cb4afcc4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" makubwa_hebu-makubwa-umri-tayari"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" makubwa"," userResponse":" makubwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543686919561","data":{"timestamp":" 1543686919561"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203759"," gameId":" 551ffdaa-8932-4e5e-808a-d673cb4afcc4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbele_mbele-hebu-si-baadaye"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" mbele"," userResponse":" mbele"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543686934524","data":{"timestamp":" 1543686934522"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203759"," gameId":" 551ffdaa-8932-4e5e-808a-d673cb4afcc4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" mbele_mbele-hebu-si-baadaye"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543686934671","data":{"timestamp":" 1543686934671"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_203759"," gameId":" 551ffdaa-8932-4e5e-808a-d673cb4afcc4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je una meno mangapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANGAPI"," userResponse":" MANGAPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}